(Howard:)Okay. Well, so the reason that might
sound crazy is because it's crazy!
(Raj:)Look, Howard, you're in a relationship.
(Raj:)You know you have to make
compromises.
(Howard:)Yes, but my compromises
are about which bedspread to buy...
(Howard:)...or whose turn it is to do the laundry,
Bernadette's or my mom's.
(Raj:)It's a great deal.
We both get our parents off our backs.
l don't have to come home
to an empty apartment.
(Raj:)Plus, once I'm married, I can finally eat
carbs again and let myseIf go.
(Howard:)Why don't you tell your parents
you wanna try to find someone else?
You know, one who hasn't slept
with more women than you.
(Raj:)Because this one wants to marry me.
l might never find another one who does.
You're thinking about marrying someone
you're never gonna have sex with?
l can't believe your attitude.
l thought you were in favor
of gay people getting married.
(Howard:)Yes, to other gay people.